(dark music)
(match striking)
(upbeat music)
- There's a fine line between
the things
we choose to remember and
those we choose to forget.
Memories are like incomplete
stories in that way.
And the one I'm gonna tell you
is about love. loss. family.
and some pretty fucking
bad decision-making.
(upbeat music continues)
This is a cautionary tale
about a girl who got dealt a
shitty hand
and tried to do something about
it.
I know. I know.
You get what you get
and you don't get upset.
Well. I'm upset.
(gun firing)
Let me start from the beginning.
- [Speaker 1] Oh my gosh. there
she is.
- [Speaker 2] Say hi. girls.
What are you doing.
- [Fox] My sister Spooky
and I were inseparable.
But then Dad T-boned an 18
wheeler
and everything went to shit
after that.
Mom's casual alcoholism turned
into
a not so casual drug problem.
and suddenly I became
public enemy number one.
Mom. stop! You can't keep doing
this.
- [Mom] Don't touch that.
- [Fox] Please. Mom!
- [Mom] Get the fuck out!
I said get the fuck outta my
house!
- Fine!
(door slamming)
I can't stay here anymore.
I'm done.
- Where are you gonna go?
- [Fox] I'm not sure.
I can't keep fighting with her.
(soft music playing distantly)
- [Spooky] But what about me?
(soft music continues)
- You.
You.
could have this whole
room all to yourself.
- [Spooky] I don't want you to
go.
(tense music)
- There's food in the fridge.
and that should last you a
couple of days.
And then I put the number for
the pizza place by the phone.
(dramatic music)
- [Spooky] Promise you
won't forget about me?
(sentimental music)
- [Fox] I'll be honest.
I don't really remember much
after that.
(sentimental music continues)
That is. until she came along.
Goldie. my first love.
- Hi. honey.
(soft funky music)
You look like you could
use a little bit of help.
- [Fox] Some might call this
the beginning of the end.
(engine revving)
(rock music)
But for a minute there. it was
glorious.
(rock music)
Ever love someone so much.
you'd follow them straight into
hell?
Yeah. me too.
("Fox on the Run" by Sweet)
(door slamming)
See. the thing about dating a
drug dealer
is that they're always
looking for the next payday.
♪ I don't wanna know your name ♪
♪ 'Cause you don't look the same
♪
- [Fox] And nothing's ever
enough.
♪ You think you got a pretty
face ♪
♪ But the rest of you is out of
place ♪
♪ You looked all right before ♪
- [Fox] And if you're
making money on one vice.
might as well make money on all
of them.
("Fox on the Run" continues)
- Here you go. honey.
- [Fox] Sure. it looks like a
party.
- Get in there.
- [Fox] But it stops being fun
when you can't get off the ride.
- That's my girl.
♪ You. you talk about just every
band ♪
♪ But the names you drop are
second-hand ♪
- But then last night. I saw
her.
It was my little sister.
(glass smashing)
It was Spooky.
- Where you going?
- Let go of me!
Spooky!
(people shouting)
Spooky! Spooky!
Spooky! Spooky! Spooky!
And that's when I knew.
I was gonna get back
to her no matter what.
Now. getting out of here
unnoticed wasn't gonna be easy.
(light music)
Oh. didn't I mention. it was a
full house?
That's Crystal. the bleeding
heart.
And that's Minx. the hothead.
(banging on table)
Good people that lost
their way. Sound familiar?
Neither have family. so they
took to this one pretty quick.
Then there's Ricky and
Domino. the bruiser twins.
They've done Goldie's dirty work
ever since she made their
pervy daddy disappear.
(Ricky laughing)
Those guys can eat a dick.
(upbeat music)
See. Goldie had no one.
so she collected all of us
like little fucking dolls.
to keep locked up in her little
dollhouse.
And she'll fight hard
and she'll fight dirty
to keep what's hers.
(dramatic music)
- I love you.
Okay. let's eat.
- How you feeling. Boss?
- Fantastic.
Barring our little
whoopsies from last night.
Turns out the juice was worth
the squeeze.
and we are on the precipice
of very lucrative deal.
This time next week. we
will have a real pool.
My dad always said that you
can turn any hand into gold.
Just depends on how you play it.
And. well. doesn't hurt
to know the dealer.
To my old man.
who would be rolling over in his
grave
if he could see me now.
Never underestimate the power
of being underestimated.
- Or how many dime bags
it takes to fill a pool.
(Crystal coughing)
- What was that?
- A joke.
- Do you think that
you can do a better job
at providing for us. is that it?
Articulate.
- No.
- Well. I guess we know Fox
isn't the funny one of the
group.
(group laughing)
(banging on table)
(tense music)
(dog barking)
(traffic passing)
(tense music)
- [Police Officer]
Breaker. what's your 20?
- 912. suspicious person
on scene. standing by.
- [Police Officer] Need you back
at the station to meet the new
recruit.
- You mean the brown-noser?
- [Police Officer] Breaker. be
nice.
- Well. I guess it makes sense
you wanted her to learn from the
best.
- [Police Officer] That's the
spirit.
(Breaker chuckling)
- [Breaker] Good old
Goldie. always on the money.
(tense music)
Let's go to work.
(rock music)
- Shit.
- Howdy.
- You're not Rocco. are you?
- I'm gonna need you to pass
me your keys nice and slow.
Thank you.
Why don't you hop out of the
car?
How old are you?
- I'm 16.
- Jesus Christ.
- Look. I got my license
and registration inside.
- Cool.
- All right. all right. This
ain't my car.
This is my cousin's car.
and he's doing some time.
And he just said to look after
it.
Wait. wait. wait. wait. wait.
wait. wait.
I know this looks bad.
but I swear. I swear.
I've never done this before.
Please. just please let
me go. don't do anything.
(gun firing)
(tense music)
(tense music continues)
- Fox?
Fox?
Come here.
Let me look at you. let's see.
Oh. sweetheart.
Oh. you took a bad tumble.
That was too hard. I'm so sorry.
I just don't understand
what's gotten into you.
Ever since last night.
- Spooky!
I just wanted to talk to her.
- Oh. sweetheart. that wasn't
anybody.
You trust me. don't you?
We're gonna make you all
better. okay? I promise.
(Goldie humming)
(camera shutter clicking)
(shutter clicking)
(water spraying)
- [Radio Host] All your
most intimate fantasies.
- You ever think about getting
outta here?
- Why?
- I mean. don't you want more
than this?
- Everything I want is right
here.
(zipper zipping)
(dog barking)
(officers chattering on radio)
(door closing)
- Breaker. our new recruit
wanted to see you in action.
Officer Kelly Corbett. former
SFPD. We're lucky to have her.
- Sergeant Breaker. it's
so nice to meet you.
I've heard a lot about you.
- Yeah.
- So. what happened here?
- Well. I witnessed the perp
dealing.
so I drew on him. told him not
to move.
He came at me with a knife
when I was searching the car.
Left me no other choice but to
shoot him.
(tense music)
- There's nothing here.
- That's how I found it. short
stack.
- Don't do that.
- Corbett. let's go
meet with the other team
members.
(lid closing)
- Look forward to working
together. Sergeant.
- Yeah.
Not for fucking long.
(phone ringing)
- Yep?
- Breaker?
- It's done.
- [Goldie] Good. Kept it tidy?
- Not exactly. One casualty.
- Sloppy.
- [Breaker] Well. I had
to given the size of it.
- Hmm. How much are we talking?
- Enough snow to cancel school
for a year.
- Huh. Well. we'll see you
tonight then. Billy Boy.
I'll put the girls down early.
- Yeah.
(pensive music)
(rock music)
(girls yelling and laughing)
(rock music continues)
- My girls.
we have a little celebrating to
do.
(tense music)
(owl hooting)
(eerie music)
Never forget.
our family.
is thicker than blood.
(eerie music)
I love you.
(tense music)
Thick. thick. thicker thank
blood.
Thicker than blood.
(rock music)
(girls talking)
(tense music)
(girls hooting and yelling)
- [Spooky] Catch me!
- Spooky!
Spooky. I'm coming!
(upbeat music)
Spooky!
(pop music)
(camera shutter clicking)
(eerie music)
(car running)
(car door closing)
I'd recognize that stupid hat
anywhere.
Breaker. Goldie's bagman.
They've been burying money
in the ground for years.
and I happen to know
exactly where they stash it.
(rock music)
(rock music continues)
(cars shuffling)
- Ah. Billy Boy.
(rock music)
Oh. Fuck the small talk. I
guess.
- Just open it.
(zipper unzipping)
- Holy-
- Half a million. Even
split. right down the middle.
- And when did you become such
a greedy little thumbsucker?
- I made it happen. didn't I?
- On my tip.
You know. if I didn't know any
better.
I'd think you were
getting ready to retire.
- Everything we've done before
this
is child's play in comparison.
- I've got people to feed.
Billy.
- And I'm risking everything.
(tense music)
- Okay. Sarge.
Just this once.
50-50.
Because you deserve it.
We gotta move it in one clip.
though.
Set up a game night. Let
the gangs do what they do.
Doc Rogers rides with the trust.
Ugly motherfucker. but he's
clean.
- Fine. Just lemme know when.
(dark music)
- Doc. Goldie.
I got a big one for you.
I'll see you Friday night.
Thanks. Doc.
Voila.
Now. how about a smile?
- Yeah.
- Your cut from the last job.
Pleasure as always.
(dark music)
(car starting)
Stash it.
(tense music)
(ATV attempting to start)
(high-tension music)
(thug whistling)
(tense music)
(door creaking)
(door closing)
(owl hooting)
(thug whistling)
(eerie music)
(ATV starting)
- Hey.
(tense music)
Where's Fox?
Hello?
(tense music)
(rock music)
Fuck!
(rock music continues)
(pensive music)
(car rumbling)
(knocking on door)
- Spooky?
Spook?
(soft music)
Hello?
Spooky?
- [Mom] You don't think I feel
you
judging me all the time.
- Mom. stop.
- [Mom] Little miss fucking
perfect.
(soft music)
- Oh. shit. this isn't
Spooky's.
(dramatic music)
Remember when I mentioned some
pretty bad decision-making?
Well.
there's more.
(upbeat music)
- No. no. no. no. no. no. no.
no. no. no.
Where the fuck is the money?
Shit!
- Oh. come on. Pick up the
fucking phone.
(tense music)
(phone ringing)
(cards shuffling)
(rock music)
(phone ringing)
(chatter on police radio)
- Hey. this may go down
smoother.
(Breaker slurping)
Did I do something to upset you?
- Nope.
The Frogman case up north.
you must have been
really proud of yourself.
Brave Officer testifies against
her own.
Nothing like getting transferred
to a shithole town like this to
reward you
for your good behavior. huh?
- Look. I don't wanna be here
anymore than you want me here.
- Finally. something we can
agree on.
- You gonna get that?
- Nah. just the old ball and
chain.
(radio chatter)
- Where the hell have you been?
- Doing my job?
What the fuck is so important
that you keep blowing me up?
- Fox took the cargo and ran.
- I'm sorry. What'd you just
say?
- What about what I just
said? Didn't you understand?
- Are you fucking kidding me?
How does that happen?
Honestly. I laid this in your
lap.
How do you lose it?
I mean. it's not like
it's just a couple bricks.
Goldie. you fucking incompetent
junkie.
- Consider this an official
missing person's report.
- I don't fucking work for you.
- Oh. that's funny because
the pictures I have
of you snorting cocaine off
a hooker's ass say otherwise.
(upbeat music)
- [Fox] So no Spooky.
and a bag full of blow.
I had to stash the thing
somewhere.
and there was only one safe
place I could think of.
(light music)
- (gasping) Hi. Sorry.
- Sorry.
- You scared me.
- Sorry. Can I help you?
- Yeah. I was just looking for
a locker to put my things in.
- Those are for customers only.
Are you skating?
- No. No.
But.
I was hoping that
maybe
you
could
let me use it still.
- What's in the bag?
- Bricks of cocaine.
(both laughing)
- Really funny.
(bright instrumental music)
(employee screaming)
(copier running)
- Hey Sarge. I just got a call
about the
traffic light glitching on Main.
I was gonna head out before
calling Traffic Control.
- You know. Corbett. I got a
better idea.
Why don't you stay here
and type up the report
from my bust yesterday.
- With all due respect. I'm not-
- Isn't Frisco where they
invented these dumb machines?
I bet you're a star on them.
Maybe when you're done.
you can help Pam type
up our archived cases.
Women helping women. See.
I could be a feminist.
(sinister music)
- Find the girl.
Fox will come.
(sinister music)
- [Corbett] What kind of drug
dealer
assaults an officer for an
eightball?
(sinister music)
(Pam clearing her throat)
(eerie music)
Pam. right? Kelly Corbett.
- I know.
- Of course.
I wasn't sure since. you know.
we didn't have proper
introduction.
- What can I do for you.
Officer?
- Yeah.
What can you tell me about the
Sergeant?
- Well. he's got the highest
rate
of closed cases north of
Sacramento.
- [Kelly] With a record like
that.
he must be a very gifted
detective.
- [Pam] Well. the Captain
certainly thinks so.
- [Kelly] And you don't?
- [Pam] I didn't say that.
- [Kelly] Huh? Is there
anything else you can share?
(door closing)
(dark music)
- Just a word of advice.
I suggest you tread lightly.
Nothing is more dangerous than
a man who's been humiliated.
(tense music)
(knocking on door)
- Housekeeping.
(rock music)
- Man. what the fuck?
You're always such a buzzkill.
Oh. whoa. whoa. whoa. whoa.
whoa. whoa. That's her.
That's her. that's her. that's
her.
THat's the girl from the party.
Shit shit. That's her. that's
her.
Pull over. Pull over.
(dark music)
(shutter clicking)
- Want some?
What's your name?
(pensive music)
I'll tell you what.
you tell me your name
and I'll help get you outta
here.
I'll even let you drive.
(pensive music)
(door closing)
That's a pretty name.
- I hate it.
- So change it. Who cares?
Who's gonna know?
(dramatic music)
(car revving)
(car running)
(Spooky screaming)
- Spooky! Spooky!
(tires squealing)
Spooky!
(Fox crashing)
(faint middle eastern music)
What's going on?
Where am I?
- You're okay.
- Why am I here?
- Well. you kind of
ate the hood of my car.
But don't worry. your
money maker's still intact.
- Who are you?
- Me? I'm Frankie.
- [Fox] Meet Frankie.
a delusional nut job with a
heart of gold.
- Couldn't find an ID on you.
so my options were a little
limited.
I thought about calling the
cops.
but that doesn't really
go well for a Jane Doe.
Oh God. I have to get my
sister. they're gonna kill her.
- Relax. Let me. I'm
gonna get you some water.
I'll be right back.
(Fox groaning)
(pensive music)
- Come on.
A goddamn stalker.
- Wow. dude. You're like
super. super pretty man.
- Sir.
Thank you. Can you describe the
girl?
- Which one?
- Either.
- Sure. sure. sure. sure.
So. the one running down the
street.
Yeah. she was. she was pretty
hot.
And then the one that hit her.
she was pretty easy on the eyes
too.
She had this crazy like. yeah.
And. and the universe of
purple. I would say hair.
- Purple hair.
- Yeah.
- Anything else?
- Oh yeah. she was. she
was crazy strong too.
She carried that blonde chick
like she was a cutout cardboard
man.
- Blonde girl. can you
describe her height?
Short hair. long hair. anything
like that.
- She was like-
- Hey.
- Hey Sarge.
- What are you doing here?
- I got a call up about a hit
and run.
- Usual.
- Can you describe the car?
- Hell yeah.
It was one of those galaxy
blue. like Cutlasses.
- Okay. Oldsmobile blue Cutlass.
- [Counterman] Yeah.
- Did you catch any of the
numbers on the license plate?
- I think there's like a four in
it.
- Thanks.
Oh. one more thing. Do you
recognize her?
- [Counterman] Yeah. yeah. See.
I told you. she's hot. man.
- Great. Thanks a lot.
- Have a slice day.
- Hey Pam. can you pull all DMV
records
of people who own a blue
Oldsmobile...
- Hey.
- ...Cutlass in the county.
- Hey. I'm talking to you.
Where are you going?
- To find your missing girl.
- Let's get something
straight. short stack.
This is my case. Look
around. this is my town.
- Just trying to do my job.
- How noble of you.
I don't think you understand me.
You do what I let you do. Got
it?
(sinister music)
Since you're here.
we might as well put you to good
use.
Come with me.
Not that way.
- I'll go first. Frankie
DeFranco. combat medic.
Well. actually I should
say ex-combat medic.
I saw some crazy
shit and
I don't know. sometimes I still
do.
- Yeah.
- Anytime I hear the tick. tick.
tick.
It's like.
but. fun fact. sugar
always brings me back.
So anyways. I got discharged on
account
of seeing some stuff that
they told me I didn't see.
So now I'm back here just until.
you know. I find a place of my
own.
So that's me.
Your turn.
Goldie is going to kill your
sister. is that the story?
- Wait. what? How. how'd you
know?
- You were mumbling her name
while you were knocked out. so.
(gasping) Oh my God. Unless
Goldie is your sister.
- That's a long story.
- I love long stories.
- So. about this missing girl.
you gonna tell me who she is?
- Just another gutter rat.
- So what's it to you?
- Just trying to do my job.
- You know. there are smarter
ways to locate a vehicle.
- Calling me stupid. Frisco?
(tires squealing)
Looky looky here. You were
saying?
Shit.
- Hey Pam. how are we
doing on this DMV records?
- [Pam] I pulled three and
counting.
- [Kelly] Copy that.
(door closing)
- [Frankie] Wow. So what's the
plan?
- I mean. I have to go back for
my sister.
- You do realize that Goldie
is baiting you. right?
- What choice do I have?
(acoustic guitar music)
- I can think of a few.
Welcome to Habibi headquarters.
- [Fox] Whoa.
Holy shit.
- Pretty cool. huh?
- [Fox] Did you make these?
- No. my brother did.
He's obsessed with martial arts.
Well. he's not actually my
brother.
but he practically is.
His family took me in.
Speak of the devil.
- Well. hello.
- Dylan. this is uh.
- Fox.
And finally.
- Dylan.
- [Fox] Action film fanatic
with a penchant for Stallone.
- Nice to meet you.
- [Dispatch On Scanner] Injury
accident. 14th Street north.
- So Dylan. my friend Fox is
in a little bit of a situation.
- What kind of a situation?
- Think Aunty Entity.
lost tribe in Thunderdome.
bow with commando.
- No shit.
I fucking love Commando.
- What's Commando?
- Listen.
- Oh. no. no.
You know. we'll deal
with that. Look at me.
High risk expedition. everything
we've been training for.
You in?
- Yeah. I'm free. Let's do it.
- No. no. This isn't a game.
I. I'm not. no one is in. and
I'm not taking you with me.
- Listen lady. you will
not find two people
more qualified than us.
- I don't even know you.
- It's fine. She's right.
She doesn't know us or need us
or any of our stuff.
Good luck. I guess.
So you have no problem finding
your sister
and your friends all by
yourself.
- Why do you even wanna help me?
- I'm a combat medic.
helping people's what I do.
Plus I kind of owe you. the car.
- [Dispatch On Scanner]
Searching for a blue
Oldsmobile Cutlass for a hit
and run off I-99 headed east.
Driver possibly armed.
- So what's it gonna be?
Good choice.
- What now?
- Now do what they do
in every action movie.
- [Fox] Well. these two
are definitely a bad fit.
but beggars can't be choosers.
Fuck it.
(soft music)
- Ha!
- What the fuck?
(upbeat music)
- All in the wrist. okay?
- Okay.
- Come. come on again.
One. come. one two. come.
(upbeat music)
- The painkillers are really
kicking in.
- Elbow here. Boom.
Okay. here.
- No. I got it this time.
- Okay. go ahead.
- Mm-hm.
Shit!
- Stash it.
(car revving)
- Come on. one two. Yes.
(both grunting)
(upbeat music)
Come on.
(both grunting)
- Hell!
(upbeat music)
Okay.
- Dylan?
(Mom speaking in foreign
language)
- A video. mom.
- Sorry. Auntie.
- Habibi.
- Hello.
- Is your friend staying
over? The bed is made.
- Oh. no. no. no. no. no.
She's just visiting.
- And have either of you
offered her something to eat?
Haram. well. Haram. who raised
your mama?
- Are you hungry?
- Yeah.
(siren beeping)
- The Cutlass belongs to Frankie
DeFranco.
Ex-military was stationed in
Beirut
during barracks bombing in '83.
Says here she was discharged
after failing psych evaluation.
- Let me guess.
She went AWOL the second
she saw some kid bleed out.
- No. actually it says
she fired on bags of rice.
- Huh? Frankie DeFranco
does not like risotto.
- [Mom] More rice.
- [Dylan] More rice on her
plate.
- [Frankie] Mm mm mm mm.
- [Dylan] It's all really good.
- This is the most amazing
thing I've ever tasted.
- Mm.
- What's this?
- And what's this?
- Pitha.
And honestly.
this doesn't even compare
to what you get over there.
- Oh no. It's really special.
Wanna become a big actor
and do my own stunts. like
Stallone.
- He's gonna be like the
Lebanese Rocky.
- Yeah. I will.
And I'm gonna show them what
Beirut is really made of.
- You will.
- I will.
- Maybe I'll get to go someday.
- Yo. you should come with us
next time.
(Lebanese music)
- I bet Spooky would love it.
Crystal and Minks. too.
We have to get them outta there.
- Okay.
If we're gonna get through this
alive.
we need to know exactly what
we're doing
and where we're going.
Show us the lay of the land.
(acoustic guitar music)
- Okay.
Here is the main house.
and then the shed is in the
back.
It's pretty remote. there's only
one road
that leads right to the front.
so they'll see us coming.
(knocking on door)
- Do you?
- I don't know. Do you?
- No.
(doorbell ringing)
- Dylan!
- Okay. Mama.
(Dylan muffled)
Hi.
- We're here to ask you
a few questions about-
- Do you speak American?
- Yes sir. I do. I speak
three languages fluently.
- Are you Demeter?
- Yeah. I go by Dylan. but yeah.
- I'm Officer Corbett. We're
here to ask-
- We're looking for Frankie
DeFranco.
You know where she is?
- [Dylan] Seen her. is
there something wrong?
- Would you mind if I take a
look around?
- No. not not. not at all. Come
on in.
(tense music)
- [Kelly] How long have
you lived here for?
- Oh. in America? About 10
years.
- You live alone?
- No. I live. I live
with my mom and my uncle
- And Frankie?
- Frankie? Frankie. she usually
just drifts. drifts around.
Last I heard she had a
place up on Division.
- Division?
- Yeah.
- [Kelly] Great. when was
the last time you saw her?
- Last time I saw her?
Last time I saw her. two. two
weeks ago.
A week ago. a week ago. Yeah.
She was at my uncle's
restaurant.
Habibi Cafe and lounge.
- H-A-B-I.
- Yeah. B-I.
(tense music)
(door opening)
(tense music continues)
- Can I help you?
Shit.
(teapot crashing)
- Goddamn it.
- I'm really. sorry. Are you
okay?
Please. let me help you.
- No. don't.
- You want a banana?
It's really-
- No. I'm fine.
It's from my brother. then.
- Trust me. No. thank you.
- It will help with your
indigestion.
- She hurt me with her tea.
- The orange blossom tea?
- Goddamn it. lady.
I don't know what's wrong
with your fucking ears. but I
said no.
- You come into my house. poking
around.
You did not even say hello.
I offer you something.
- I think it's
time to go.
- Something I made
with my own hands.
And you say (indistinct).
- [Dylan] Mom.
- Goddamn foreigners.
(Mom speaking in foreign
language)
- Thank you. let us know
if you need anything else.
(Mom and Dylan speaking
in foreign language)
They're gone.
(tense music)
- We're fucked.
- Oh. you're back.
- Yeah. I need to do a bit of
recon.
Pam. I'll be fine. You should go
home.
- Okay.
- Before you go.
are these all of Breaker's
cases?
- All the ones he turned in.
(eerie music)
Goodnight.
- See you later.
(sinister music)
(sinister music continues)
Bingo.
(phone ringing)
- Hey.
Hello?
Goldie?
- You know.
most people are average
because they don't know the
difference
between inconvenience and
opportunity.
- What the hell is that supposed
to mean?
- It means that I'm making
lemonade
and you can't have any.
You're out Billy Boy. it's over.
- Cut the bullshit.
There wouldn't be a deal
if it weren't for me.
- Precisely. yet I can't
think of a single reason
why I need you anymore.
Enough snow to cancel
school for a year. right?
- You got it back.
- Something like that.
- Goddamn it Goldie. I did
everything you asked of me.
Okay. I brought the deal to the
table. You can't cut me out.
- Oh. come on Billy.
Did you really think that I
would let you leave me first?
Good luck with that retirement.
now.
- I'm gonna fuckin' hang
you. do you hear me?
You're fuckin' dead.
Fuckin' bitch.
(dramatic instrumental music)
(Spooky crying)
(dramatic music continues)
(door closing)
(siren blaring)
(music fading)
(door slamming)
Why you little bitch.
I'll take you all down.
(dramatic music)
- [Fox] It's not gonna work.
That cop works for Goldie.
I'm not walking you guys
into a suicide mission.
They'll kill you.
Maybe.
Better me than the girls.
(Frankie groaning)
or my sister.
- You can't go.
(pensive music)
- Okay. hold on. Goldie has one
dirty cop.
Big whoop. we can still take
them.
- No. you don't know this guy.
He'll do anything for a payday.
I should have known she
was gonna get him involved
when I took the bag.
- What bag?
- I accidentally swiped a
duffle bag full of blow.
(Frankie and Dylan chuckling)
In my defense. I thought it was
money.
- What?
You've just been walking around
with an industrial amount of
cocaine?
- No.
No. of course not.
I stashed it.
(Dylan's fingers snapping)
- This is good.
This is great.
Cobra?
- I don't know. I haven't seen
it.
- This is a classic hostage
negotiation situation.
- They have something we want.
- We have something they want.
- Yes.
- We can't just walk up to the
front door.
I mean. we've been made.
- Not all of us have been made.
We even have the getaway car.
(rock music)
This is Boss.
she was a gift from my
dad on my 18th birthday.
My uncle brought her over from
Beirut.
- Are you sure?
(upbeat music)
(car starting)
(engine revving)
(engine dying)
- (foreign phrase) She's.
she's just warming up.
She's hot. she's getting warm.
- Okay. great.
(car starting)
- Yeah.
- There we go.
(tires squealing)
(engine revving)
(upbeat music)
(knocking on door)
- Sergeant Billy Breaker.
Open up. we need to talk.
(rock music)
- [Billy] Come on. come on. come
on.
(laughing) There you are.
(rock music)
- You ready?
(door closing)
- I have some bad news.
- Fuck.
- Yeah.
But I do have some good news.
I do have some good news.
I come prepared.
Huh?
- Seriously.
(tense music)
(uptempo dance music)
(engine rumbling)
- Let's go.
(engine stops)
- Hey. what is this an
interrogation?
Come on.
- Who are you. asshole?
- Who am I. asshole?
I'm the asshole that has friends
downtown
that says you two boys might
need something that I have.
- What the?
- So let me just start
from the beginning of the story.
(dance music continues)
- Fox. is it you?
- I need you to be quiet.
- What do you mean. me?
Minx. she's back.
- Okay. we gotta go
and I need you guys to come with
me.
- Where the hell have you been?
- I've been a sinner.
- What's in the bag?
- But I ain't no crook. okay?
I'm not a crook.
Come on. huh?
I'm just trying to get to the
big
pasta and fazul up in the sky.
Y'all know what I mean?
- I never heard no gumba say.
y'all.
- Take it easy. okay?
Because I-
- You walking in like nothing
happened.
- Shit!
(ominous music)
Fuck!
(gun firing)
(Domino grunting)
Oh. come on Fox.
You don't want me to
accidentally shoot Minx. now do
you?
(gun firing)
- Okay.
- Welcome home darling.
- Fuck you. asshole.
(gun firing)
- Hey. hey. hey. hey. hey.
- Fuck you.
- Atta girl. stick it to her
like fuckin' Chinese chicken.
- I'm Japanese you dumb duck.
(all grunting)
- I know you're mad. but
I had to get my sister.
(gun firing)
- Oh.
- Let's go.
(Ricky growling)
- We're supposed to be sisters.
- We are.
- Then. why did you leave?
(somber music)
- Come on. come on guys.
We gotta go.
You gotta get us out of here.
Come on.
(somber music)
- [Ricky] Come here.
- Sisters in blood.
(others grunting)
(rock music)
- Go to the gas station. Stay
there. I'll meet you there.
I'm right behind you.
- What about you?
- I have to get Spooky.
I'll be fine.
- Okay.
(both growling and grunting)
- [Dylan] Commando.
- [Domino] Fuck Commando.
(Domino grunting)
- Here please!
- Fox.
Hey.
(Ricky grunting)
- Dylan!
(Domino growling)
(dance music continues)
- [Fox] Remember how I said I
was upset?
So. now you know.
Nuts. right?
- Fox. get Spooky.
- [Dylan] Frankie. you okay?
- [Frankie] Dylan. watch out.
(Frankie grunting)
(upbeat music)
(Domino yelling)
- Oh no.
- Yeah.
(helicopter thrumming)
(machine gun firing)
(high-tension music)
(Domino yelling)
(Domino grunting)
(Frankie yelling)
(Domino choking)
- Jihad. motherfucker.
(aircraft flying overhead)
(soft music)
- Spook?
Spooky.
(eerie music)
(slugging)
(Fox gasping)
- Say hi to the Fox.
(Fox grunting)
But you see I'm smart.
So come on kid.
Where's my stuff?
(Fox grunting)
Sweetheart.
where is my bag?
- Fuck you!
(Billy slugging)
(Fox yelling)
(Billy laughing)
(Fox panting)
Wow.
Okay. here's the deal.
You give me what I want.
and I promise I'll buy you a new
crown.
Hell. I'll get you veneers.
Tell me where it is and I'll
let you walk right outta here.
- [Fox] Let me go. and
I'll tell you where it is.
- Yeah. you're still not gettin'
it.
You don't get to fucking
negotiate.
What the fuck?
Wow.
I'm gonna take a wild guess
here.
but I think this probably
has something to do with it.
You are so lame.
Goodnight. now.
(door closing)
(Fox grunting)
(Billy laughing)
(door closing)
(truck starting)
Jesus!
Move!
Good morning. motherfucker.
- Oh my God.
- It happened.
- Are you okay?
- Yeah. I'm fine.
Sugar helps.
- Okay.
- But did you find Spooky.
No. no. no. no. I'm gonna
go look in the shed.
- No? Okay.
Wait. Fox.
- Oh. Oh Jesus. don't throw it.
Dyl. you good?
- See the other guy?
- Okay. yeah.
Oh. is he dead?
- I don't think so.
- [Crystal] Move. move asshole!
- I don't think you know who
you're messing with. okay?
- Take that. you little bitch.
- How tall are you?
- [Minx] Tall enough to kick
your ass.
- [Crystal] Hit him again.
(Minx slugging)
(siren beeping)
- Freeze. drop the weapon. Drop
it.
- Frisco. you're just in
time. They're fucking crazy.
- Women helping women. am I
right?
(gun firing)
- Ah! Fuck!
You shot my foot.
- What are ya gonna do. report
me?
Sergeant Billy Breaker.
you're under arrest for
obstruction of justice.
- What the fuck?
- Possession with the
intent to distribute.
- What are you doing?
Fraud and
tampering with evidence.
- We can make a deal. okay?
40-60. I've already got a buyer.
- You have the right to remain
silent.
Anything you say...
- 50-50.
- ...can and will be used
against you in a court of law.
- I don't think you know
how much money...
- You have a right
to an attorney.
- ...we're talking about.
- If you can't afford one.
one will be provided for you.
Do you understand the rights
that I've just read to you?
And with this in mind. do you
have anything else to say?
- I need to go to a hospital.
- Watch your head.
(Billy grunting)
- [Billy] My foot.
- Put your hands on the hood
now.
(tense music)
- Took you long enough.
You've made a real mess. Fox.
- I have what you want.
but I need you to let her go
first.
(Goldie chuckling)
- Look at you.
a real business woman.
But did you forget?
I know you
better than anyone.
I know the real you.
- What are you talking about?
- Oh. you really did get
lost in the lie. girly.
The mind really is wild. isn't
it?
Protecting you from what you
did.
so the guilt wouldn't kill you.
So let's take a trip down
memory lane. shall we?
- Stop.
- Spooky is dead.
- Because you weren't there to
help her.
You do remember.
if you try hard enough.
don't you. Isabel?
Isabelle. Isabel. Isabel.
Isabel.
- [Speaker] Isabel. get over
here.
Come on. Wake up.
She won't wake up. Isabel.
Isabel?
Please.
Come on (indistinct).
Isabel!
- She's a grown woman.
she can handle herself.
- [Speaker] Please don't leave.
(solemn music)
- Enough.
- Get the fuck out of here.
You do remember.
- Spooky?
Spooky?
Spooky!
(eerie music)
No!
She slipped.
- And that's why I brought you
here.
so that you could just start all
over.
You can start all over.
I just wanna help you. okay?
- No.
- I just want to help
you like I always have.
Come here.
Let me help you. my baby.
(Fox crying)
It's okay.
You're gonna be okay.
(sad music)
(Fox crying)
You see it now. don't you?
I wasn't lying.
There's nobody else out there
for you.
except me.
(Fox crying)
Us.
your family.
(dramatic music)
Bad beat.
Now. you're gonna give me the
bag.
and then I'm going to put you
down
like the sick puppy that you
are.
(Fox screaming)
(Goldie grunting)
(Fox grunting)
Where's the fucking bag?
(screaming)
(dramatic music)
(Fox grunting)
(Fox gasping)
(Goldie panting)
(dramatic music)
(Fox gasping)
(lighter clicking)
I loved you. you know?
I taught you everything.
I thought you were strong
enough.
What was that?
(Fox mumbling)
How many times
do I have to tell you to
articulate?
- I said.
you underestimated me.
(Goldie gasping)
I loved you too.
(Fox yelling)
(ambient music)
(Fox crying)
(Fox panting)
(soft music)
(dramatic music)
(dramatic music continues)
- [Fox] Turns out that fine
line between what we remember
and what we forget. can save us.
I couldn't save Spooky.
but somehow
she saved me.
I guess Goldie was right.
the mind really is wild.
- Fox?
Fox?
Is this yours?
- Yeah. it's mine.
What happens now?
As far as I'm concerned.
this case is closed.
Guess I'll see you guys around
soon.
("Fox on the Run" by Sweet)
- Always good to see you. Doc.
Take care.
♪ I don't want to know your name
♪
♪ 'Cause you don't look the same
(Minx cheering)
- [Fox] It's funny.
whoever said you can't choose
your family
really had no idea what
they were talking about.
because I did.
I'd say I hit the jackpot.
♪ You looked all right before ♪
♪ Fox on the run ♪
♪ You scream and everybody
comes a-running ♪
♪ Take a run and hide yourself
away ♪
♪ Foxy is on the run ♪
♪ Foxy ♪
♪ Fox on the run ♪
♪ And hide away ♪
(rock music)
♪ You. talk about just every
band ♪
♪ But the names you drop are
second-hand ♪
♪ I've heard it all before ♪
♪ I don't wanna know your name ♪
♪ But you don't look the same ♪
♪ The way you did before ♪
♪ Fox on the run ♪
♪ You scream and everybody
comes a-running ♪
♪ Take a run and hide yourself
away ♪
♪ Fox is on the run ♪
♪ Foxy ♪
♪ Fox on the run ♪
♪ And hide away ♪
(rock music)
♪ Foxy ♪
♪ Fox on the run ♪
♪ You scream and everybody
comes a-running ♪
♪ Take a run and hide yourself
away ♪
♪ Fox is on the run ♪
♪ Foxy ♪
♪ Fox on the run ♪
♪ And hide away ♪
(soft music)
(soft music continues)
(upbeat music)
(upbeat music continues)
(slow rock music)
(rock music continues)